Guide to the Lewis and Clark Centennial and American Pacific Exposition and Oriental Fair Records 1894-1933
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Division of Concessions and Admissions (John A. Wakefield), Series 8
  - Correspondence, general
    - Allender (lunch counter/restaurant); Allison (admission devices), 1905 (Box-folder 41/15)
    - Aloe (optical co.); American Boy Jumper Co., 1905 (Box-folder 41/16)
    - American Box Ball Co.; American DeForest Wireless Telegraph Co., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/17)
    - American Electric Novelty Mfg. Co.; American Family Magazine, 1905 (Box-folder 41/18)
    - American Inn Restaurants / Hotels, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/19)
    - American Olive Co.; Ames (Old Plantation), 1905 (Box-folder 41/20)
    - Anderson (Ladies Aux. to World's Fair); Anderson (glove cleaning), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/21)
    - Anderson (playing cards); Anderson & Duniway Co. (Official Guide), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/22)
    - Angst (stenographers/typewriters); Anderson (import merchants), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/23)
    - Angelica Embroidery Co.; Annin & Co. (flags), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/24)
    - Apex Cigar and Vending Machine Co.; Armard (naval show), 1905 (Box-folder 41/25)
    - Archer & Schanz Co. (chewing gum); Armstrong (peanut/popcorn), 1905 (Box-folder 41/26)
    - Art Metal Works Selling Co.; Art Novelty Manufacturing Co., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/27)
    - Asay (Indian relics); Asselstine (souvenir goods), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/28)
    - Asher (teas); Ashton-Smith (souvenir/novelty), 1905 (Box-folder 41/29)
    - Atherton (eye glasses); Atkinson (gold and silver pins), 1905 (Box-folder 41/30)
    - Attenberg (souvenirs); Averill (sea shell articles), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/31)
    - Avery (merry-go-round); Augustus (Jubilee Singers), 1903-1904 (Box-folder 41/32)
    - Aune (photographer); Automatic Stamping Machine Co., 1904 (Box-folder 41/33)
    - Aydelott (Giant Swing); Ayers (Glass Works), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/1)
    - Axtater (L & C Souvenir Gold Dollars); Bacon (Official Program), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Bahr (lunch and refreshments); Baird (Congress of States), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/3)
    - Baker, F.H. (Merry-go-Round); Baker, F.R (Optical), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - Baker, Geo. L. (Davenport Farms); Baker, W.H. (Chocolate), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - Baldwin Airship Co.; Baldwin, Capt T.S. (Captive Balloons), 1905 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - Baldwin Health Tablets; Bale (ice cream cornucopia), 1905 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - Bales, A.C.; Ball, Bert (Info Request), 1905 (Box-folder 42/8)
    - Ballou, F.A. (Steam Yachts); Banane, Sol (Oriental Concession), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/9)
    - Bancroft, T.D. (Souvenirs); Bankston, John W. (Game); Bannell, Eleanor (Music); Barber (Jewelry), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/10)
    - Barbecue Catering Co.; Barchres, Eliza R. (Art Pictures); Bard, Jas F. (Ladies Toilet Items), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/11)
    - Barlow, W.G. (Maple Sugar); Barnard, Archibald (Centrifugal Merry-go-Round); Barnes, Samuel (Toilet Concession), 1905 (Box-folder 42/12)
    - Barnes, W.H. (Diving Elks); Barnes, W.J. (Soft Drinks); Barns (St. Louis Timberman), 1905 (Box-folder 42/13)
    - Baroody, Dr. Alex (Tomb of Christ); Barry, J.W. (Wild & Trained Animals); Barry, Thos. (Automobile Concession), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/14)
    - Bartlett, Charles W. (Popcorn); Barton, J.C. (Vaudeville Theater); Barveleben, F. von (Post Cards), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/15)
    - Barveleben, F.Von (Souvenirs); Bass, Carleton (Bull Fight); Batarse, Francis (Mexican Art Work), 1905 (Box-folder 42/16)
    - Bates, L. (Amusement Supplier); Batie, Robert (The Old Plantation); Bauer, Fritz (Champayne), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/17)
    - Bayliss, Ed.M. (Land of the Midnight Sun), (Roast Beef Sandwich), (Darkness & Dawn), 1903-1905 (Box-folder 42/18)
    - Beech, Frank W. (Biographical History); Beaumont, Dr. G.H. (Optical Goods); Beck, A.M. (Amusement), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/19)
    - Becker, H.W. (Info Request); Becker, L.A. (Soda Fountain); Bedbury, W.F. (Novelties), 1905 (Box-folder 42/20)
    - Bedford, L. R. (Candy-Electric); Bee Publishing (Sunday Bee); Beecham, Capt. R.K. (Lewis & Clark Souvenirs), 1905 (Box-folder 42/21)
    - Begg, Jonathan (Electric Railroad); Bell, C.A. (Mummies); Bell, Frank W. (Chinese Concession), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/22)
    - Bell, George (Gem Stones); Bell, H.M. (Candy Sales); Bellman, L.E. (Stringed Instruments), 1905 (Box-folder 42/23)
    - Belmont, M.A (Souvenirs); Belvedere Music Hall Co., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/24)
    - Benedict, Chas. (Orange Cider); Bengiant, H.E. & Son (Art Museum), 1904 (Box-folder 42/25)
    - Benham, J.W. (Indian Goods); Bennett, E.W. & Co. (Metal Polish); Bennett, Mark (Press Correspondence), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/26)
    - Bennett, Orin (Lunch Counter); Bennerscheid, A. (Spanish American War); Benson, Chas. D. (Concessions), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/27)
    - Benson, Geo. (Amusement); Bentley, Wm. (Wire-work); Bentley, Will A. (Trained Chickens), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/28)
    - Berell, W. (In re Mr. Kauffman); Bergman, E. (Souvenirs); Bergson, N. (Opticals), 1905 (Box-folder 42/29)
    - Berkowitz, L. & Co. (Shooting Gallery); Bernstein, R. Alex. (Indian Exhibit); Best, Ernest M. (Spectacular Show), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/30)
    - Bethel, John D. (Bakery); Bhumgara & Co. (General Corrspondence); Bickett, Wm. E. (Aerialists); Bird, W.D. (Info Request), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/31)
    - Birkinbine, John (Acknowledge Pass Receipt); Bishwati, Kalil (Soft Drinks) No File; Bissell, Chas. B. (Merry-go-Round), 1905 (Box-folder 42/32)
    - Black, C.R. (House Wrecking); Blackwell, Mrs. L.S. (Shopping); Blake, E.L. (Official Guide), 1905 (Box-folder 42/33)
    - Blanke Tea & Coffee Co.; Blimcoe, Dr. A.G. (Souvenirs); Blitz, F.R. (Manager, Millie Christine), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/34)
    - Bogardus, Capt. A.H. (Shooting Gallery); Bohart & Leighton (Soda Fountain); Bolles, S.W. (Official Catalogue), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/35)
    - Bomberger, A.C. (Souvenirs); Bone, E.H (Souvenirs); Bonebrake, P.C. )Peanuts and Popcorn), 1905 (Box-folder 42/36)
    - Bonner, Mrs. M.T. (Transportation); Bonta, Mrs. E.E. (Homemade Confectionary); Brooker, Louis F. (Novelties), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/37)
    - Booth, E.L. (Info request); Bopp, Louis (Carrousal); Bordon's Condensed Milk Co., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 42/38)
    - Borland, A.M. (Cider); Borelli & Vitelli (Novelties); Borosepsine Medical Co. (Medication), 1905 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - Boston, Dr. Ernest (Opticals); Boswell, Capt Ben I. (Mineral Water); Botsford, A.M. (Guitar/Mandolin Player), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/2)
    - Bouillon, Jos. (List of Concessions); Bouery, Mick (Ice Cream Sandwich); Bourveau, Belle (Oregon Wood Novelties), 1905 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - Bowser, Mrs. L. (Restaurant); Bowyer T.J. (Info Request); Boyd, Mrs. C.A. (Rustic Maze), 1905 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - Boyce, Chas. A. (Sand Blasting Maching); Bracklin, M.R. (Shetland Ponies); Brady, Hugh J. (Parcel Checking), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - Brant & Donahue (Whip and Cane); Brantingham, M.L. (Back Support); Breen, Harry (Log Rolling Contest), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - Bren, Weiss and Goldgraber (Penny Arcade); Brendler, Edw. R. (Info Request); Breton, Harry & Gertrude (Aero-Cycle), 1905 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - Bridgman, W.E. (Souvenir Art Book); Brierton, F.H.E. (Candy & Popcorn); Breitwiser, J.E. (Souvenirs), 1905 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - Bright, H.V. (Turn Stiles/Ticket Choppers); British Columbia Agricultural Association; Brock, H.E. (Photos on Postal Cards), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/9)
    - Brooks, Frank (Baloon Exhibit); Brooks, H.M. (Info Request); Brown, Anna S. (Painted Oyster Shells), 1905 (Box-folder 43/10)
    - Brown, Carl (Carl's Cartoon Cactus); Brown, E.P. (Solar Steam Engine); Brown, F.M. (Personal Correspondence), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - Brown, F.M. (Ostrich Farm); Brown, George Stairs (Crockery & China Souvenirs); Brown, H. (Pocket Knives), 1904 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - Brown, Nathaniel (Legal Matters); Brown, W.T. (Large Heavy Man); Bryant, Wilson (Cleaning Concessions), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - Bucher, H.A. (Roller Chairs); Buell, S.W. (Candy/Popcorn, etc.); Buffalo Music Co., 1905 (Box-folder 43/14)
    - Burger, Bertha (Employment); Burgess, B.H. (Info Request); Burghardt, W.A. (Merry-go-Round), 1905 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - Burke, J.T. (Trained Animals); Burham, L.B. (Info Request); Burns, O.S. (Amusements), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/16)
    - Burns, Augusta (Optical); Burrelle's Press Clipping Bureau; Busch, Frank (Ice Cream Sandwiches), 1905 (Box-folder 43/17)
    - Bushby, Geo. G. (Novelty Wheel); Bushong & Co. (Tickets); Buthillier, F.K.A. (Railroad Track), 1905 (Box-folder 43/18)
    - Butte, C.C. (Restaurant); Butte, P.C. (Miniature Electric Railroad); Butterfield Bros. (Optical), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/19)
    - Butterworth, Chas. (Photographer's Association); Butterworth & Smelhurst (Silk Manufacturing Looms); Buzzacott, Col. (Camp Lewis), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/20)
    - Byers, Lee (Roller Chair); Bylaws Lewis & Clark Exposition; Byrnes, John F. (Amusements), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/21)
    - Cagney Brothers (Miniature Railroad); Cain, C.V. (Watrous Hot Pan Lifters); California Biscuit Co. (Amritam); California Pear Mfg. Co. (Abalone Shells), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/22)
    - California Radium Co.; Callaghan, Florence C. (Candy Kitchen); Cameron, Geo. J. (Guides), 1905 (Box-folder 43/23)
    - Camilla (Beauty & Toilet Preparations); Campbell, Archie (Novelties); Campbell, David (Branding Scene); Canan, C.J. (Oil Paintings), 1905 (Box-folder 43/24)
    - Canihad, J.F. (Animal Show); Cann, (Toilets); Cann (Weiner Wurst); Card, St. Gro. (Lunch Counter /Novelties), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/25)
    - Carley, Horace S. (The Burning Ship); Carlisle, R.C. (Historical Wild West Exhibit); Carlson, Oliver (Info Request); Carnahan, D.S. (Lunch Counter), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/26)
    - Carpenter, Frank (Bears); Carpenter, W.J. & Co. (Photographic Supplies); Carque, Otto (California Grape Juice); Carr, A.B. (Indian Curios), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/27)
    - Carr, M.P. (Embroidered Goods); Carr, T.F. (Mounted Birds/Animals); Carter, G.K. (Lunch Counter); Carter, R.W. (Roller Chairs), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/28)
    - Carver, W.F. (Diving Horses); Casey, N.S. (Indelible Stamping Outfits); Castleman, Humphreys (L & C Souvenir Gold Dollars), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/29)
    - Caswell, R.B. (Chopper Boxes); Cauzac, Jean A. (Turkish Harem Dancing Girls); Central Mfg. Co. (Toilet Cream), 1905 (Box-folder 43/30)
    - Central Press Bureau; Century Cash Register Co.; Century Dictionary & Cyclopedia, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/31)
    - Ceylon Planters Tea Co.; Chambers, A.B. (Cigars & Tobaccos); Crescent Real Estate & Investment Co., circa 1905 (Box-folder 43/32)
    - Chamberlain, F.D. (Ref The Morgan Co.); Chamla, Gabriel (Chinaware, etc.); Chance, N.H. (Automatic Stamping Machines), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/33)
    - Channing, G.E. (Post Cards); Chapin, W.H. (Flag Emblem); Chapman, C.C. (Souvenirs); Charlton, Paul (Personal Correspondence), 1903-1905 (Box-folder 43/34)
    - Chase, A.D. & T. Griffith (The Spirit Bridge); Chase, Clement (Omaha Excelsior); Chester & Edwards (Spokane Daily News), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/35)
    - Chicago House Wrecking Co.; Chicago Vaporizer Co.; Childs, J.E. (Donkey Fortune Telling Machine), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/36)
    - Christy, Frank (Umatilla County Pack-train & Trading Post); Clapp, Albion B. (Toboggan Slide); Clark, J.D. (Metal Engraving), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/37)
    - Clark, John R. (Lunch Counter); Clark, T.J. (Balloon/Airship); Clarke, C.R. (Sandwich Stand), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/38)
    - Clarke, Graff ( List of concessions); Clarke, H.C. (Purchase Chairs); Clarke, H.T. (Missouri River Imp. Assoc.); Clarke, Henry T. (Hat Tree), 1905 (Box-folder 43/39)
    - Clarkson, T.S. (Automobiles, Use of), 1904-1905; undated (Box-folder 43/40)
    - Clatt, H.A. (Orange Cider); Clausen, J. (Soft Drinks, etc.); Clauss Shear Co., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/41)
    - Clay, E.C. & Co. (Medicinal Articles); Cleary, Thos. (Popcorn & Peanuts); Clossett & Devers (Delivery Wagon), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 43/42)
    - Coan, Geo. F. (Photography); Coast Agency (Typewriters & Office Supplies); Cohen, I. Lesser (Postal Cards), 1903-1905 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Cohen, Jesse (Info Request); Cohn, Morris (Saloon & Lunch); Coin Counting Machine Co., 1905 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - Coleman, Z.Y. (Turnstiles/Chopper Boxes); Colgate Perfumes; Collins Marine Wireless Telephone; Colson, C.H. (Arrival Time Gov. Hunt), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Comeford, J.H. (Ref. Mike Golden); Commercial Stamp Trade Journal, 1905; undated (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Committee of Concessions & Admissions (List of Concessions & Sample Agreements), 1905 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - Condon, D.E. (Spiral Tower), 1906 (Box-folder 44/6)
      Includes photograph of model of Spiral Tower
    - Condon, D.E. (Spiral Tower—Blueprints), undated (Box-folder Oversize Folder)
      Detailed scale drawings of tower, 11 sheets
    - Conkling, Frank E. (Lunch Counter); Conlon, Marie (Lunch Stand); Connell, Samuel (Correspondence), 1903-1905 (Box-folder 44/7)
    - Conrad, Wm. J. (Wood Novelties); Consolidated Chicle Co.; Cook, C.E. (Parcel Checking), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/8)
    - Cooke, Edw. G. (Biblical Spectacle); Cooke, Mrs. M.C. (Souvenir Watch fobs); Cooley, James R. (Restaurant Concession), 1904 (Box-folder 44/9)
    - Coopey, Charles (Uniforms); Cordray, J.F. (Trained Animals); Cornwall, Geo. N. (Oregon Timberman), 1905 (Box-folder 44/10)
    - Correll, W.O. (Turnstiles/Chopper Boxes); Cosgrove, Robert H. (Turnstiles/Chopper Boxes); Cottrell, L.R. (Eating House), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/11)
    - Coughanour, W.A. (Large Steer); Cowan, Harry (Optical Concession); Crabbe, James Irving (Booklet Concession), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/12)
    - Crabill, John (Parcel Checking); Craddick, T.A. (Restaurant Concession); Craig, A.L. (Blue Grotto Concession), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/13)
    - Craig, J.R. (Chiquita, The Doll Lady); Crane, Geo S. (Amusement Concession); Cranwell, A.J. (Jewelry Concession), 1903-1905 (Box-folder 44/14)
    - Craven. O.F. (Jewelry Concession); Crawford, Capt, Jack (Poet Scout); Creighton, K.B. (Fortune Telling), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/15)
    - Cretors & Co. (Peanuts/Popcorn); Crocker, J.W. (Railway Conductors Excursion); Croft, Lee (Miniature Easels), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/16)
    - Crofut, A.H. (Hot Candy/Cracker-jacks); Crofut, W.H. (Candy Concession); Croin, John (Holland Bakery), 1905 (Box-folder 44/17)
    - Crook, Oliver J. (Ice Cream Concession); Croom, Elya (Music Composition); Crothers, O.M. (Restaurant), 1905 (Box-folder 44/18)
    - Crow, Davis & Benge (Folding Stool); Crowley, George C. (Newspapers); Cullen, R.P. (Optical Concession), 1905 (Box-folder 44/19)
    - Cunningham, M.F. (Correspondence); Cunningham, M.N. (Info Request); Cunningham, J. Vance (Dermal Preparations), 1905 (Box-folder 44/20)
    - Curtis, F. (Band Saw); Curtis, G.W. (Mexican Articles); Cushman, Lewis L. (Restaurant), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/21)
    - Cusick, Jas. (Ice Cream Concession); Cusick, W.H. (Cider Concession); Cuthbert, F. (Novelties), 1905 (Box-folder 44/22)
    - Cutillo, Prof. B. (Musician); Cryderman, Geo (Novelties), 1905 (Box-folder 44/23)
    - Daggett, M.E. & McRae (Candy Concession); Dale, Lou (Naval Show); Dallas, E.M. (Optical), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/24)
    - Daniel, W.S. (Info Request); Darlow, A.C. (Transportation); Darowish, G.B. (Turkish Confectionary), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/25)
    - Darwin, J.H. (Character Reading); Davenport, Homer (The Davenport Farm); Davidson & Leigh (Miniature Railroad), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/26)
    - Davis, B.D. (Candy/Refreshments); Davis, Chick (Photography); Davis, E.B. (Ticket Sales), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/27)
    - Davis, E.T. (Palmist Concession); Davis and Barth's Electric Theater; Davis, Glen L. (Soft Drinks), 1905 (Box-folder 44/28)
    - Davis, J.P. (Restaurant/Bar); Davis, N.S. (Peanut Roaster); Davis, Sue L. (Lecturer), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/29)
    - Davis, O.G. (Info Request); Davis, Sam'l P. (Mining Exhibit); Davis, Walter S. (Chocolate Concession); Davis, Wilbur C. (Info Request), 1905 (Box-folder 44/30)
    - Davidson, F.B., Chief, Department of Admissions, 1905 (Box-folder 44/31)
    - Day, H.S. (Info Request); De Baumel, Emile (Electric Engraving); DeBevoiser, J.L. (Reference Room Rental), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/32)
    - DeHart, Wm. (Sandwiches); d'Hemecourt, Jules A. (Sash and Blind Lock); Delroy, Arthur (Psychic Entertainment), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/33)
    - DeMora, Jane (Face Creams); Dennis, W.B. (Blackbutte Quicksilver Mine); Deputy, H.E. (Ice Cream), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 44/34)
    - DeRackin, S.E. (Igorrote Village); DeWees, J.W. (Novelties); DeWitt,, Hugo & Mayer (Jewelry), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/1)
    - Dexter, A.H. (Trained Wild Animals); Dey, W.C. (Candy Sales); Diamant, Henry A. (Silver Spoons), 1905 (Box-folder 45/2)
    - Dickey, Dr. Wm. (Optical Concession); Dill, W.L. (Info Request); Dirnberger, G.A. (Popcorn/Peanuts), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - Ditmar, E.L. (Restaurant); Doane, J.W. (Peanuts); Dockarty, A.J. (Indian Goods and Curios), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/4)
    - Dodd Mead & Co. (Lewis & Clark Book); Dodds, George W. (Peanuts/Popcorn); Dolan, W.F. (Turnstiles/Chopper Boxes), 1903-1905 (Box-folder 45/5)
    - Donnell, J.C. (Info Request); Donnelly, A. (Soft Drinks); Donahee, M.F. (Novelties), 1903-1905 (Box-folder 45/6)
    - Donovan, W.F. (Optical Concession); Doren Ventilating Sash, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/7)
    - Dosch, Col. H.E. (Director of Exhibits, General Correspondence), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/8)
    - Dosch, Col. H.W.(Director of Exhibits, Foreign Correspondence), 1905 (Box-folder 45/9)
    - Doubleday Page & Co.; Douthit, Mary L. (Books/Souvenirs); Dover Manufacturing Co., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/10)
    - Dowd, D.T. (Restaurant); Dows, W.G. (Bottle Washing), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/11)
    - Earhart, K.H. (Door Maze); Early, Chas. E. (Mt. Hood Railroad Co.); Eastern Manufacturer's Co., 1905 (Box-folder 45/12)
    - Eberhard, George F. (Asbestos Sad Irons); Eberle & Turner (Restaurant); Edgreen, A. (Receipt), 1904 (Box-folder 45/13)
    - Edlefsen, A.H. (Postal Cards); Edmonds, Elmer (Roller Chair Concession); Edwards-Huntzinger Mfg. Co. (Souvenirs), 1903-1905 (Box-folder 45/14)
    - Edwards, H.E. (Info Request); Edwards, Jas. E. (Info Request); Edwards, Nora (Skirt Support), 1905 (Box-folder 45/15)
    - Egan, J.G. (Toilet Concession); Egan, Jas T. (Confetti); Egan, W.B. (Newport Opera House), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/16)
    - Eger, J.B. (Portrait Sketches); Egry Autographic Register Co.; Ehle, Chester (Music & Stamps), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/17)
    - Ehrke, Ernest (Jewelry); Electric Novelty Co.; Elzas & Co. (Dutch Wafers), 1905 (Box-folder 45/18)
    - Gerz, Louis - Pfahler, Charles B., 1905 (Box-folder 45/19)
      Gerz, Louis (Optical)
      Griffin, Lucia B. (memory test)
      Oregon Railroad & Navigation Co. (shipment from St. Louis)
      Palmateer, E. N.
      Pezur, Jake (Cider)
      Pfahler, Charles B. (re: amounts due from concessionaires)
    - S, General, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/20-21)
      Note: there are no files in this subseries for the letters F-R.
    - Sc-Sei, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/22)
    - Schenkein, Dr. Samuel, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/23)
    - Schmidt, H. A., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 45/24)
    - Scott, Thomas (South Sea Island Exhibit), 1904 (Box-folder 45/25)
    - Sel-Si, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 46/1)
    - Sh-St, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 46/2)
    - Strauss, J. B.—Blueprints for Arch Pavilion or Hanging Roof Garden, 1904 Sept. 8 (Box-folder Oversize Folder)
    - Sias, O. B., 1904 (Box-folder 46/3)
    - Sprague, William (American Boy Day), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 46/4)
      Includes program for American Boy Day at the Louisiana Purchase Exposition, 1904
    - Sullivan, John L., 1905 (Box-folder 46/5)
      Includes photographs of John L. Sullivan
    - T, General, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 46/6-8)
    - U, General, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 46/9)
    - V, General, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 47/1)
    - W, General, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 47/2-6)
    - W, General, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 48/1-2)
    - W-Z, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 48/3)
    - Wittenberg, Herman, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 48/4)
    - Woodard & Tiernan Printing, 1905 (Box-folder 48/5)
    - YWCA Restaurant, 1905 (Box-folder 48/6)
    - Zerbe, Farran (Sale of Lewis & Clark Coins), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 48/7)
  - Correspondence between John A. Wakefield and Henry E. Reed, 1905 (Box-folder 48/8-9)
    See also series "Division of Expoitations—Wakefield, John" below.
  - Correspondence Scrapbook, 1905 (Box-folder 108/1)
    Cover title: "Advices from the President and Director of C and A." Primarily letters to and from F. B. Davison, Chief of Admissions. Also includes press releases laid in.
  - Drawings of Flower Hut and Japanese Hut, undated (Box-folder 123/2)
  - Employees, List of, Division of Concessions and Admissions, 1905 (Box-folder 49/1)
  - Ephemera, circa 1904-1905 (Box-folder 49/2)
    Includes booklets from Louisiana Purchase Exposition, 1904, and catalog of office furniture.
  - "Following the Trail" (Details of Proposed Amusements), circa 1904 (Box-folder 49/3)
  - Inside Inn (St. Louis) financial statements, 1904 (Box-folder 49/4)
  - Inside Inn (St. Louis) floor plans and photographs, 1904 (Box-folder 123/9)
  - List of Concessions to be Given Medals, 1905 Oct. 12 (Box-folder 49/5)
  - Menchen's Johnstown Flood—Blueprints (2 sheets), 1905 (Box-folder Oversize Folder)
  - Monthly Time Book, 1905 (Box-folder 49/6)
    Ledger book containing names of employees of the Division, their hours and pay.
  - Passes
    - Applications for Passes and Monthly Coupons, 1905
      - May, 1905 May (Box-folder 49/7-11)
      - June, Part 1, 1905 June (Box-folder 49/12)
      - June, Parts 2-6, 1905 June (Box-folder 50/1-5)
      - July, Parts 1-5, 1905 July (Box-folder 50/6-10)
      - July, Parts 6-7, 1905 July (Box-folder 51/1-2)
      - August, 1905 Aug. (Box-folder 51/3-8)
      - September, Parts 1-2, 1905 Sept. (Box-folder 51/9-10)
      - September, Parts 3-7, 1905 Sept. (Box-folder 52/1-5)
      - October, Parts 1-6, 1905 Oct. (Box-folder 52/5-11)
      - October, Parts 7-9, 1905 Oct. (Box-folder 53/1-3)
    - Applications for Workmen's Passes, Parts 1-3, 1905 (Box-folder 53/4-6)
    - Applications for Workmen's Passes, Parts 4-6, 1905 (Box-folder 54/1-3)
    - Passes for Concessionaires, 1905 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Pass Record (bound ledger volume), 1905 (Box-folder 104/1)
    - Stop Lists of Montly Photographic Passes, 1905 (Box-folder 54/5-7)
  - Record of Commutation Tickets Issued, circa 1905 (Box-folder 55/1)
  - Uniforms and Badges, 1905 (Box-folder 55/2)
- Division of Exhibits (Henry E. Dosch), Series 9
  - Acceptance of Exhibits
    Forms listing materials received through customs. Some forms include detailed list of items received.
    - Bernard, Croin, Kohn, Moser, Munk, Perk, Shelby, Taussig, TerBrock, 1905 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - British Empire, 1905 (Box-folder 55/4)
    - France, 1905 (Box-folder 55/5)
    - Germany, 1905 (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Italian I, 1905 (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Italian II, 1905 (Box-folder 55/8)
    - Japan I, 1905 (Box-folder 55/9)
    - Japan II, 1905 (Box-folder 55/10)
    - Japan III, 1905 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Livestock, 1905 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Russian; Hungarian; Chinese; Philppines; Holland; Denmark; India; East India; Cairo; unidentified., 1905 (Box-folder 56/3)
  - Acceptance of Space, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 56/4)